

# Llazar Dhimitri

Nationality: Albanian Date of birth: 11/09/1999 Gender: Male

Phone number: (+355) 672009581 Email address: <a href="mailto:llazardhimitri5@gmail.com">llazardhimitri5@gmail.com</a>

in LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/llazar-dhimitri-23037820a

O Home: Street Abedin Pasha, 1015 Tirana (Albania)

### **ABOUT ME**

I am an electronic engineer with professional experience in technical support, data engineering, and network engineering. Over this period I have developed a deep understanding of various aspects of the technology industry, including troubleshooting hardware and software issues, designing and implementing data pipelines, and managing network infrastructure. Recently I have been training in software development area working with programming languages like Java(Spring Framework), JavaScript, Angular, HTML, CSS and also with databases like MySQL. Apart from the technical work, I have several other interests that I am passionate about. I have a keen eye for design and enjoy creating compelling visual content. I also like to stay active and pursue the love for sports. I am an avid runner and enjoys training for marathons and other endurance events like playing football, basketball and volleyball.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Field O&M Network Engineer

MakHes Albania [ 06/02/2023 - Current ]

City: Tirana
Country: Albania

Website: https://www.makhes.com.al/

- 1. Determine the issue with the network infrastructure and identifie a misconfigured switch as the root cause. Configuring the switch and restore the connectivity to the affected users.
- 2. Coordinating with various departments for the proper planning and execution using GIS and SAP for maintenance and service work.

## **Data Delivery Engineer**

**Engage3 powered by dexi** [ 03/10/2022 - 03/02/2023 ]

City: Tirana
Country: Albania

Website: https://www.engage3.com/

- 1. Using web programming languages like JavaScript, HMTL and CSS to develop analytical tools for collecting data.
- 2. Responsible for managing recurring data needs with time-sensitive deliverable.

### **Technical Support**

ALBtelecom [ 02/08/2021 - 31/05/2022 ]

**City:** Tirana **Country:** Albania

Website: <a href="https://www.one.al/">https://www.one.al/</a>

- 1. Troubleshoot system and network problems, diagnosing, solving hardware and software faults using different portals for measuring the line parameters, reseting, configuring and adding channel packages.
- 2. Provide needed information on IT products or services.

### Client advisor

Neptun [ 13/04/2021 - 30/06/2021 ]

City: Tirana
Country: Albania

Website: https://www.neptun.al/

- 1. Detailed presentation and demonstration of the functionality for each item.
- 2. Giving details and functions for all the products.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **BSc Electronic Engineering**

**Polytechnic University of Tirana** [ 15/10/2018 - 26/07/2021 ]

Address: Boulevard Deshmoret e Kombit Nr 4, 1011 Tirana (Albania)

Website: https://www.upt.al/

### **Full-Stack JAVA Developer**

**Software Development Academy** [ 24/09/2022 – Current ] **Address:** Street Papa Gjon Pali II 1010, Tirana, (Albania)

Website: https://sdacademy.al/

## Java Developer Internship

**IKONS** [ 07/03/2023 – Current ]

Address: Street Dervish Hima, Tirana (Albania)

Website: https://ikons-see.com/

#### **Home automation Internship**

**2Smart Systems** [ 25/05/2021 - 22/06/2021 ]

Address: Street Papa Gjon Pali II ABA Business Center, Floor 7, 1011 Tirana (Albania)

Website: https://2smart.al/

### Volunteer

M & M Ivanaj Foundation Institut [ 19/10/2019 - Current ]

Address: Street Perlat Rexhepi, Tirana, (Albania)

Website: https://ivanaj-foundations.org/

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Albanian

### Other language(s):

### **English**

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING B2

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

#### **Technical skills**

Java / JavaScript / Framework: Spring, Hibernate, SpringBoot / MySQL / HTML/ CSS

# Organisational/managerial skills

Decision-making / Team-work oriented / Analytical skills / Creativity

## **Communication skills**

Confident and articulate professional speaking abilities